The Amanda Seals Show.
Our group chat topic of the week.
Are you turning into your mama?
Let's go to the phone lines.
When I was younger, my mama would always say on the way to school,
she would be like, you know, I want a quiet ride.
I want a quiet ride.
So we wondering why is it at 6 o'clock in the morning,
we just waking up, you got an attitude, you're stressed out,
and you're telling us you want a quiet ride.
Well, now I didn't have three kids and myself.
I mean, when I get up in the morning, I'm tired.
So I find myself telling my kids every morning,
be quiet.
I want a quiet ride.
I don't want to hear all that first thing this morning.
I just love it because these things are so Pacific.
Like people really are like, I was told this.
I didn't understand.
Now I do.
I really feel like some of it is just like being an adult.
Like you were just never going to know until you became an adult
and you were like, oh, okay.
Like my mom used to always be like, I'm burnt out.
I am burnt out.
And I'd be like, goddamn.
Why are you all burnt out?
Now I'm over here like, ugh, I'm burnt out.
Like I had a very strict bedtime and it wasn't until I was older.
And this isn't something that I turned into, but she explained to me,
she was like, you had to be in bed by eight because I needed those next two hours
to just exist without you.
That's a parental hack.
When my youngest was in the first grade, he used to go to bed at 7.30.
Lights out.
You know, those are the things that you just don't realize.
So I'm like, why do I have to go to bed?
She's like, it's shut it down.
My time.
Right.